* Solutions
    
* Services
    
    * By content
    * By use cases
    * By file type
    * By languages
    
* Company

* Sign in
* Translate now

Select a translation service

[Human Pro Translation Edited by an expert, fast delivery time, $0.07 per word](https://www.translate.com/order) [Machine Translation Unedited. Instant. Free.](https://www.translate.com/machine-translation)

Terms of Service
================

* Privacy Policy for clients
* Terms & Conditions for clients
* Privacy Policy for translators
* Terms & Conditions for translators

**Privacy Policy**
------------------

**Last updated and effective: December 16th, 2024**

**Purpose**

Translate.com LLC ("us", "we", or "our") operates Translate.com website (the "Service").

This page informs you of our policies regarding the collection, use, and disclosure of personal data pertaining to each of our unregistered visitors, registered customers in connection with their access and use of our Service and the choices they have associated with that data.

We use your data to provide and improve the Service. By using the Service, you agree to the collection and use of information in accordance with this policy. Unless otherwise defined in this Privacy Policy, terms used in this Privacy Policy have the same meanings as in our Terms and Conditions, accessible from Translate.com

**Definitions**

* **Service**  
    Service is the document translation from the specified source language into the specified target language and the editing of the specified translations provided via Translate.com website
* **Personal Data**  
    Personal Data means data about a living individual who can be identified from those data (or from those and other information either in our possession or likely to come into our possession).
* **Usage Data**  
    Usage Data is data collected automatically either generated by the use of the Service or from the Service infrastructure itself (for example, the duration of a page visit). It may include information such as your computer's Internet Protocol address (e.g. IP address), browser type, browser version, the pages of our Service that you visit, the time and date of your visit, the time spent on those pages, unique device identifiers and other diagnostic data.
* **Cookies**  
    Cookies are small pieces of data which may include an anonymous unique identifier stored on your device (computer or mobile device).
* **Data Controller**  
    Data Controller means the natural or legal person who (either alone or jointly or in common with other persons) determines the purposes for which and the manner in which any personal information are, or are to be, processed. For the purpose of this Privacy Policy, we are a Data Controller of your Personal Data.
* **Data Processors (or Service Providers)**  
    Data Processor (or Service Provider) means any natural or legal person who processes the data on behalf of the Data Controller. We may use the services of various Service Providers in order to process your data more effectively.
* **Data Subject (Unregistered Visitor, Registered Customer)**  
    Data Subject is any living individual who is using our Service and is the subject of Personal Data.

**Information Collection and Use**

We collect several different types of information for various purposes to provide and improve our Service to you.

**Types of Data Collected**

**Personal Data**

While using our Service, we may ask you to provide us with certain personally identifiable information that can be used to contact or identify you ("Personal Data").

We may use your Personal Data to contact you with newsletters, marketing or promotional materials and other information that may be of interest to you, including service updates and money-saving deals. You may opt out of receiving any, or all, of these communications from us by following the unsubscribe link or the instructions provided in any email we send.

_Personal Data of Registered Customers_

Personally identifiable information of registered customers may include, but is not limited to:

* Email address
* First name and last name
* Phone number
* Address, State, Province, ZIP/Postal code, City (collected until February, 1, 2022)
* Cookies and Usage Data
* Support ticket content (Zendesk, Salesforce and Desk.com customers)

_Personal Data of Unregistered Visitors_

For unregistered visitors we use only cookies to keep track of the domains from which they visit and to measure visitors\` activity on [Translate.com](https://www.translate.com/), as well as usage data collected during such visits.

**Tracking & Cookies Data**

We use cookies and similar tracking technologies to track the activity on our Service and hold certain information.

Cookies are sent to your browser from a website and stored on your device. Tracking technologies also used are beacons, tags, and scripts to collect and track information and to improve and analyze our Service.

You can adjust the settings within your web browser in accordance with your personal preferences. You can delete cookies that have already been installed at any time and reject new cookies by configuring the settings within your browser. However, if you do not accept cookies, you may not be able to use some portions of our Service.

Examples of Cookies we use:

* Session Cookies. We use Session Cookies to operate our Service.
* Preference Cookies. We use Preference Cookies to remember your preferences and various settings.
* Security Cookies. We use Security Cookies for security purposes.
* Advertising Cookies. Advertising Cookies are used to serve you with advertisements that may be relevant to you and your interests.

**Use of Data**

Translate.com LLC uses the collected data for various purposes:

* To provide and maintain our Service
* To notify you about changes to our Service
* To allow you to participate in interactive features of our Service when you choose to do so
* To provide customer support
* To gather analysis or valuable information so that we can improve our Service
* To monitor the usage of our Service
* To maintain statistics
* To provide you with news, special offers and general information about other goods, services and events which we offer that are similar to those that you have already purchased or enquired about unless you have opted not to receive such information

**Legal Basis for Processing Personal Data Under General Data Protection Regulation (GDPR)**

If you are from the European Economic Area (EEA), our legal basis for collecting and using the personal information described in this Privacy Policy depends on the Personal Data we collect and the specific context in which we collect it.

Translate.com LLC may process your Personal Data because:

* We need to perform a contract with you
* You have given us permission to do so
* The processing is in our legitimate interests and it's not overridden by your rights
* For payment processing purposes
* To comply with the law

We will not sell or provide your data to any third party where you have not provided your consent to do so. All other data is processed in accordance with the General Data Protection Regulation (GDPR) 2018 and other applicable laws.

**Retention of Data**

Translate.com LLC will retain your Personal Data only for as long as is necessary for the purposes set out in this Privacy Policy. We will retain and use your Personal Data to the extent necessary to comply with our legal obligations (for example, if we are required to retain your data to comply with applicable laws), resolve disputes, and enforce our legal agreements and policies.

Translate.com LLC will also retain Usage Data for internal analysis purposes. Usage Data is generally retained for a shorter period of time, except when this data is used to strengthen the security or to improve the functionality of our Service, or we are legally obligated to retain this data for longer time periods.

**Transfer of Data**

Your information, including Personal Data, may be transferred to — and maintained on — computers located outside of your state, province, country or other governmental jurisdiction where the data protection laws may differ from those from your jurisdiction.

If you are located outside the United States and choose to provide information to us, please note that we transfer the data, including Personal Data, to the United States and process it there. Your consent to this Privacy Policy followed by your submission of such information represents your agreement to that transfer.

We notify that the country to which personal data is transferred does not provide for an adequate level of data protection based on the European Commission decision. We endeavor to apply suitable safeguards to protect the privacy and security of your personal data and to use it only consistent with your relationship with Us and the practices described in this Privacy Policy.

**Disclosure of Data**

**Business Transaction**

If Translate.com LLC is involved in a merger, acquisition or asset sale, your Personal Data may be transferred. We will provide notice before your Personal Data is transferred and becomes subject to a different Privacy Policy.

**Disclosure for Law Enforcement**

Under certain circumstances, Translate.com LLC may be required to disclose your Personal Data if required to do so by law or in response to valid requests by public authorities (e.g. a court or a government agency).

**Legal Requirements**

Translate.com LLC may disclose your Personal Data in the good faith belief that such action is necessary to:

* To comply with a legal obligation
* To protect and defend the rights or property of Translate.com LLC
* To prevent or investigate possible wrongdoing in connection with the Service
* To protect the personal safety of users of the Service or the public
* To protect against legal liability

**Security of Data**

We implement the most commonly usedtechnical and organizational measures to ensure the protection and security of the data:

* Access control is designed to protect all physical access to the server, client and/or data rooms by using keys, authentication, authorization and other procedures.
* We ensure that all the authorized parties can access only the data specifically related to their specific tasks and/or authorization without being allowed to see anything else.
* If user data is required for analytical and statistical purposes the pseudonymization principle is followed by replacing user-related data by random, anonymous blocks of text.
* We ensure that the data is always transmitted using strong in-transit encryption standards (SSL/TLS certificates). Moreover, other secure connections are used to transfer data from web-based service containing forms, login screens, upload/download capabilities and so on.
* We ensure that all the relevant data is subject to regular backups and also regularly check them to ensure that the data can be successfully retrieved.

The security of your data is important to us, but remember that no method of transmission over the Internet, or method of electronic storage is 100% secure. While we strive to use commercially acceptable means to protect your Personal Data, we cannot guarantee its absolute security.

**"Do Not Track" Signals**

We do not support Do Not Track ("DNT"). Do Not Track is a preference you can set in your web browser to inform websites that you do not want to be tracked. You can enable or disable Do Not Track by visiting the preferences or settings page of your web browser.

**Your Data Protection Rights Under General Data Protection Regulation (GDPR)**

If you are a resident of the European Economic Area (EEA), you have certain data protection rights. Translate.com LLC aims to take reasonable steps to allow you to correct, amend, delete, or limit the use of your Personal Data.

If you wish to be informed what Personal Data we hold about you and if you want it to be removed from our systems, please contact us via email by sending your request to [support@translate.com](mailto:support@translate.com) or through a contact form on the Site.

In certain circumstances, you have the following data protection rights:

* **The right to access,** update or to delete the information we have on you. Whenever made possible, you can access, update or request deletion of your Personal Data directly within your account settings section. If you are unable to perform these actions yourself, please contact us to assist you.
* **The right of rectification**. You have the right to have your information rectified if that information is inaccurate or incomplete.
* **The right to object**. You have the right to object to our processing of your Personal Data.
* **The right of restriction**. You have the right to request that we restrict the processing of your personal information.
* **The right to data portability**. You have the right to be provided with a copy of the information we have on you in a structured, machine-readable and commonly used format.
* **The right to withdraw consent**. You also have the right to withdraw your consent at any time where Translate.com LLC relied on your consent to process your personal information.

You have the right to complain to a Data Protection Authority about our collection and use of your Personal Data. For more information, please contact your local data protection authority in the European Economic Area (EEA).

**Service Providers**

We may employ third party companies and individuals to facilitate our Service ("Service Providers"), to provide the Service on our behalf, to perform Service-related services or to assist us in analyzing how our Service is used.

These third parties have access to your Personal Data only to perform these tasks on our behalf and are obligated not to disclose or use it for any other purpose.

* Analytic  
    We may use third-party Service Providers to monitor and analyze the use of our Service.
* Google Analytics  
    Google Analytics is a web analytics service offered by Google that tracks and reports website traffic. Google uses the data collected to track and monitor the use of our Service. This data is shared with other Google services. Google may use the collected data to contextualize and personalize the ads of its own advertising network.You can opt-out of having made your activity on the Service available to Google Analytics by installing the Google Analytics opt-out browser add-on. The add-on prevents the Google Analytics JavaScript (ga.js, analytics.js, and dc.js) from sharing information with Google Analytics about visits activity. For more information on the privacy practices of Google, please visit the Google Privacy & Terms web page: [http://www.google.com/intl/en/policies/privacy/](http://www.google.com/intl/en/policies/privacy/)
* Hotjar  
    Hotjar is a technology service that helps us better understand our users' experience (e.g. how much time they spend on which pages, which links they choose to click, what users do and don't like, etc.) and this enables us to build and maintain our service by means of user feedback. Hotjar uses cookies and other technologies to collect data on our users' behavior and their devices (in particular the IP address of the device (captured and stored only in anonymized form), device screen size, device type (unique device identifiers), browser information, geographic location (country only), preferred language used to display our website). Hotjar stores this information in a pseudonymized user profile. Neither Hotjar nor we will ever use this information to identify individual users or to match it with further data on an individual user. For further details, please see [Hotjar's Privacy Policy](https://www.hotjar.com/legal/policies/privacy).  
    If you do not want to be recorded by Hotjar, you can disable it by setting the DoNotTrack header in your browser. For more information and more about Hotjar's data processing, please visit: [www.hotjar.com/legal/compliance/opt-out](https://www.hotjar.com/legal/compliance/opt-out).
* Advertising  
    We may use third-party Service Providers to show advertisements to you to help support and maintain our Service.
* Google AdSense & DoubleClick Cookie  
    Google, as a third-party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on our Service. Google's use of the DoubleClick cookie enables it and its partners to serve ads to our users based on their visit to our Service or other websites on the Internet. You may opt out of the use of the DoubleClick Cookie for interest-based advertising by visiting the Google Ads Settings web page: [http://www.google.com/ads/preferences/](http://www.google.com/ads/preferences/)
* Ezoic  
    This website uses the services of Ezoic Inc. (“Ezoic”), including to manage third-party interest-based advertising. Ezoic may employ a variety of technologies on this website, including tools to serve content, display advertisements and enable advertising to visitors of this website, which may utilize first and third-party cookies.  
    A cookie is a small text file sent to your device by a web server that enables the website to remember information about your browsing activity. First-party cookies are created by the site you are visiting, while third-party cookies are set by domains other than the one you're visiting. Ezoic and our partners may place third-party cookies, tags, beacons, pixels, and similar technologies to monitor interactions with advertisements and optimize ad targeting. Please note that disabling cookies may limit access to certain content and features on the website, and rejecting cookies does not eliminate advertisements but will result in non-personalized advertising. You can find more information about cookies and how to manage them [here](https://allaboutcookies.org/).  
    The following information may be collected, used, and stored in a cookie when serving personalized ads:
* IP address
* Operating system type and version
* Device type
* Language preferences
* Web browser type
* Email (in a hashed or encrypted form)  
    Ezoic and its partners may use this data in combination with information that has been independently collected to deliver targeted advertisements across various platforms and websites. Ezoic’s partners may also gather additional data, such as unique IDs, advertising IDs, geolocation data, usage data, device information, traffic data, referral sources, and interactions between users and websites or advertisements, to create audience segments for targeted advertising across different devices, browsers, and apps. You can find more information about interest-based advertising and how to manage them [here](https://youradchoices.com/).  
    You can view Ezoic’s privacy policy [here](https://ezoic.com/privacy/), or for additional information about Ezoic’s advertising and other partners, you can view Ezoic’s advertising partners [here](https://www.ezoic.com/privacy-policy/advertising-partners/).
* Translators, editors  
    Translators, editors provide Services of translation or editing of translations in accordance with Terms & Conditions for Service Providers due to which they might process your personal data if contained in the documents submitted for translation, editing. Other than that, translators, editors do not have any access to your personal data. They are obliged to treat all your information in confidence and shall not reproduce, otherwise use or distribute it.

**Links to Other Sites**

Our Service may contain links to other sites that are not operated by us. If you click on a third-party link, you will be directed to that third party's site. We strongly advise you to review the Privacy Policy of every site you visit.

We have no control over and assume no responsibility for the content, privacy policies or practices of any third-party sites or services.

**Children's Privacy**

Our Service does not address anyone under the age of 18 ("Children").

We do not knowingly collect personally identifiable information from anyone under the age of 18. If you are a parent or guardian and you are aware that your Child has provided us with Personal Data, please contact us. If we become aware that we have collected Personal Data from children without verification of parental consent, we take steps to remove that information from our servers.

**Changes to This Privacy Policy**

We may update our Privacy Policy from time to time. We will notify you of any changes by posting the new Privacy Policy on this page.

We will let you know via email and/or a prominent notice on our Service, prior to the change becoming effective and update the "effective date" at the top of this Privacy Policy.

You are advised to review this Privacy Policy periodically for any changes. Changes to this Privacy Policy are effective when they are posted on this page.

**Right to Equal Service**

We will not discriminate against You because you exercised any of your rights, including, but not limited to, by:

* Denying goods or services to you.
* Charging different prices or rates for goods or services, including through the use of discounts or other benefits or imposing penalties.
* Providing a different level or quality of goods or services to you.
* Suggesting that you will receive a different price or rate for goods or services or a different level or quality of goods or services.

**Contact Us**

If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, please contact us:

* By mail: Translate.com LLC, 571 S. Washington, Afton, WY 83110, United States
* By email: [support@translate.com](mailto:support@translate.com) or through a contact form on the Site

Terms of Service for Unregistered Visitors, Registered Customers
----------------------------------------------------------------

Review Date: January 10th, 2024

**Purpose**

Translate.com LLC ("We," "us," "our") provides its services (the “Service(s)”) to you through its website Translate.com ("Site"), subject to the following Terms of Service (as amended from time to time, the "Terms of Service," “Terms”). We reserve the right, at our sole discretion, to change or modify portions of these Terms of Service at any time.

Any changes will be posted on this page including the most recent revision date. We will also notify you, either through the user interface, in an email notification or through other reasonable means. Your continued use of the Service after the date any such changes become effective constitutes your acceptance of the new Terms of Service.

If you do not agree to abide by these or any future Terms, do not use or access (or continue to use or access) the Site.

In addition, when using certain services, you will be subject to any additional terms applicable to such services that may be posted on the Site or provided to you from time to time, including, without limitation, the Privacy Policy located here. All such terms are hereby incorporated by reference into these Terms of Service.

**Human Translation Content Policy**

We do not provide human translations for the following types of content:

* Texts that require creativity or where brand image is at stake
* Safety-critical texts or material where human life may be at risk in case of error
* Texts that contain profanity or sexually explicit material

No refunds or translations will be given for these types of human translation requests.

**Use of our Service**

**Services Description**

The Service is designed to provide accurate and efficient document translation from the specified source language into the specified target language (‘Translation(s)”) by the means of automatic machine translation, followed by post-machine editing by native human translators and the revision of a specified translation by qualified professional editors (“Service Providers”). You place an order for Translation by submitting an electronic order form on the Site and completing the payment. After placing an order, you cannot make changes to the order unless they are negligible and before Translations are subject to post-machine editing by native human translations or revision by qualified professional editors. In all other instances, you will be charged additionally for the Services already provided.

**Registration**

In order to access and use certain features of our Services concerning human translations, you may be required to register an account. Unregistered visitors may access only automatic machine translation. If you choose to register for the Service, you agree to provide and maintain true, accurate, current and complete information about yourself as prompted by our registration form. The information that we collect shall be governed by our Privacy Policy.

Those under 13 years of age are not authorized to use this Site or our Services, with or without registering. In addition, if you are under 18 years old, you may use the Service, with or without registering, only with the approval of your parent or guardian.

**Member Account, Password and Security**

You are responsible for maintaining the confidentiality of your password and account, if any, and are fully responsible for any and all activities that occur under your password or account. You agree to (a) immediately notify us of any unauthorized use of your password or account or any other breach of security, and (b) ensure that you log out from your account at the end of each session when accessing the Service. We will not be liable for any loss or damage arising from your failure to comply with this Section.

**Modifications to Service**

We reserve the right to modify or discontinue, temporarily or permanently, the Service (or any part thereof) with or without notice. You agree that we will not be liable to you or to any third party for any modification, suspension or discontinuance of the Service.

**Use and Storage**

You acknowledge that we may establish general practices and limits concerning use of the Service, including without limitation the maximum period of time that documents, data or other content will be retained by the Service and the maximum storage space that will be allotted on our servers on your behalf. You agree that we have no responsibility or liability for the deletion or failure to store any documents, data or other content maintained or uploaded by the Service. You acknowledge that we reserve the right to terminate accounts that are inactive for an extended period of time. You further acknowledge that we reserve the right to change these general practices and limits at any time, in our sole discretion, with or without notice.

**User Conduct**

You are solely responsible for all documents, information, data, text, images, software, photographs, graphics, messages or other materials ("content") that you upload, post, publish or display (hereinafter, "upload") or email or otherwise use via the Service. We reserve the right to investigate and take appropriate legal action against anyone who, in our sole discretion, violates this provision, including without limitation, removing the offending content from the Service, suspending or terminating the account of such violators and reporting you to the law enforcement authorities. You agree to not use the Service to:

* email or otherwise upload any content that (i) infringes any intellectual property or other proprietary rights of any party; (ii) you do not have a right to upload under any law or under contractual or fiduciary relationships; (iii) contains software viruses or any other computer code, files or programs designed to interrupt, destroy or limit the functionality of the Site; (iv) poses or creates a privacy or security risk to any person; (v) constitutes unsolicited or unauthorized advertising, promotional materials, commercial activities or any other form of solicitation; (vi) is unlawful, harmful, threatening, abusive, harassing, tortious, excessively violent, defamatory, vulgar, obscene, pornographic, libelous, invasive of another's privacy, hateful racially, ethnically or otherwise objectionable; or (vii) in the sole judgment of Translate.com, is objectionable or which restricts or inhibits any other person from using or enjoying the Service, or which may expose Translate.com or its users to any harm or liability of any type;
* interfere with or disrupt the Site, Service or servers or networks connected to the Site or Service;
* violate any applicable local, state, national or international law, or any regulations having the force of law;
* impersonate any person or entity, or falsely state or otherwise misrepresent your affiliation with a person or entity;
* harvest or collect email addresses or other contact information of other users;
* promote criminal activity;
* obtain or attempt to access any materials or information through any means not intentionally made available or provided for through the Service.

**Fees & Payment**

Payment may be required in order to use some aspects of our Service. Payments will be processed through a third-party credit card processor and you agree to abide by its terms policies.

You agree to pay us the amount that is specified in the Service in accordance with the terms available on the Pricing Page of the Site. We offer various plans which allow you to choose what works best for you.

In any case your payment for our Service cannot be less than the minimum one. The minimum payment is the lowest amount of money you are required to pay for an order that would be charged from your bank account. Our minimum payment rates reflect the terms and conditions of payment providers and their commission fees, as well as the amount of effort required to complete your order. Currently minimum payments are as follows:

* $5 for the translation of files with 166 words or less in the following formats: .pdf, .doc, .docx, .ppt, .pptx, .odt, .rtf, .xliff .csv .xls .po .indd .idml .ai .fig;
* $ 4.5 for the translation of texts via the order form on the Website, as well as files in .txt, .json formats, that contain 50 words or less;
* $ 0.5 for orders via the translation API and Zendesk Translation App.

Orders in excess of the above minimal thresholds are calculated using the formula: price per one word x number of words.

You should always check the pricing page of the Site for the current rates before submitting an order as our pricing policy is subject to change.

Depending on the plan you choose, we may bill you monthly based on the number of words translated, or may bill you when your account hits a specified amount as defined on our Pricing Page. A plan may include a limited number of translated words and therefore an additional charge may be applied for overages which may be billed monthly or when the account reaches a specified amount. We reserve the right to change our prices, including minimum payments, and will provide notice of the change on the Site. Your continued use of the Service after the price change becomes effective constitutes your agreement to pay the changed amount. You shall be responsible for all taxes associated with Services other than U.S. taxes based on our net income.

**Your plan shall automatically renew for subsequent periods of the same length as the initial term unless either party gives the other written notice of termination at least thirty (30) days prior to expiration of the then-current term. For example, if you are on a monthly plan, you will be automatically charged each month until you provide us notice you do not wish to continue the service. If you cancel in the middle of the month, you will not be entitled to a refund for the remainder of the month. If you pay for an annual plan, you will be automatically renewed for another year on your renewal date. If you do not wish to renew your plan, please provide us notice of your intention.**

If you make any major changes to an order which is already in progress, you might be required to pay for the work already performed with the respect to that order.

You are entitled to rollover any remaining unused Services during the term of your plan and 30 (thirty) calendar days after its termination. This provision applies solely to the business clients that pay on the basis of a plan.

**Delivery** **& Acceptance of Translations**

The delivery date on the Site shall be provisional provided for information purposes. We will notify you immediately if we are unable to meet a specified deadline.

All dates provided for the delivery and completion of Translations are approximate and not guaranteed. Time is not of the essence for delivery or performance, and no delay shall entitle you to reject delivery of the Service or a Translation. We will not be liable in any circumstances for the consequences of any delay in delivery or performance of the Service. All risk in the Translations shall pass to you.

In the event that you are not satisfied with our Service, you may submit a support ticket within 72 hours of receiving the product and we will redo the agreed upon translation. If you do not accept or reject a Translation within 72 hours of being notified of its completion, it will automatically be accepted.

**Intellectual Property Rights**

**Service Content, Software and Trademarks:**

You acknowledge and agree that the Service may contain content or features (collectively "Intellectual Property") protected by copyright, patent, trademark, trade secret or other proprietary rights and laws. Except as expressly authorized by Translate.com, you agree not to modify, copy, frame, scrape, rent, lease, loan, sell, distribute or create derivative works based on the Service or the Intellectual Property, in whole or in part, except that the foregoing does not apply to your own Content that you legally upload to the Service. In connection with your use of the Service you will not engage in or use any data mining, robots, scraping or similar data gathering or extraction methods. Any use of the Service or our Intellectual Property other than as specifically authorized herein is strictly prohibited. The technology and software underlying the Service or distributed in connection therewith is our property, our affiliates and our partners (the "Software"). You agree not to copy, modify, create a derivative work of, reverse engineer, reverse assemble or otherwise attempt to discover any source code, sell, assign, sublicense, or otherwise transfer any right in the Software. Any rights not expressly granted herein are reserved by us.

Nothing in these Terms should be construed as granting, by implication, estoppel, or otherwise, any license or right to use any of our trademarks or service marks displayed on the Service, without our prior written consent in each instance. All goodwill generated from the use of our Marks will inure to our exclusive benefit.

**Third Party Material:**

Translate.com shall not be liable in any way for any content or materials of any third parties (including users, translators, editors, and reviewers), including, but not limited to, any errors or omissions in any content, or for any loss or damage of any kind incurred as a result of the use of any such content. We reserve the right, although not obligated to, in our sole discretion to refuse or remove any content that is available via the Service. Without limiting the foregoing, we will have the right to remove any content that violates these Terms or is deemed by us, in our sole discretion, to be otherwise objectionable.

You agree that you must review and bear all of the risks and any damages associated with the use of any content, including any reliance on the accuracy, completeness, or usefulness of such content that may have been subject of our Services.

**Your Content:**

With respect to content or other materials you upload through the Service or share with other users or recipients (collectively, "User Content"), you represent and warrant that you own (or have sufficient rights to) all right, title and interest in and to such User Content, including, without limitation, all copyright and rights of publicity contained therein. By uploading any User Content you hereby grant and will grant Translate.com and its affiliated companies a nonexclusive, worldwide, royalty free, fully paid up, transferable, sublicensable, perpetual, irrevocable license to copy, display, upload, perform, distribute, store, modify and otherwise use your User Content in connection with the operation of the Service on your behalf, in any form, medium or technology now known or later developed. This license also includes using any User Content and corresponding translation text to enhance, refine, and improve Translate.com’s services.

You acknowledge and agree that any questions, comments, suggestions, ideas, feedback or other information about the Service ("Submissions"), provided by you to Translate.com are non-confidential and we will be entitled to the unrestricted use and dissemination of these Submissions for any purpose, commercial or otherwise, without acknowledgment or compensation to you.

You acknowledge and agree that we may preserve content and may also disclose content if required to do so by law or in the good faith belief that such preservation or disclosure is reasonably necessary to: (a) comply with legal process, applicable laws or government requests; (b) enforce these Terms; (c) respond to claims that any content violates the rights of third parties; or (d) protect the rights, property, or personal safety of Translate.com, its users and the public. You understand that the technical processing and transmission of the Service, including your content, may involve (a) transmissions over various networks; and (b) changes to conform and adapt to technical requirements of connecting networks or devices.

**Confidentiality**

We will use reasonable measures to protect any content you provide to us for the purpose of completing the Services. We will not, without your prior consent, disclose to any third party your Content, other than furnishing such information to our directors, officers, employees, agents, consultants, service providers, contractors, representatives or affiliated entities who need to have access to such Confidential Information in​ accordance with the offered Services​.​ We may be required to disclose information pursuant to lawful requests, such as subpoenas or court orders, or in compliance with applicable laws.​ Although we will use reasonable means to safeguard your information, we cannot and do not provide any guarantees regarding the effectiveness of the security we employ or our ability to prevent third parties, acting unlawfully, from obtaining information that you provide to us. We cannot and do not guarantee that any information provided to us by you will not become public under any circumstances. You should appreciate that all information submitted on the Site might potentially be publicly accessible.

**Copyrights**

You agree to be solely responsible for the use of our translations and shall be solely responsible for abiding by all copyright. We shall not be responsible for any infringements of copyright laws by you or the content you have provided us for completion of the Service. You shall not hold us liable for copyright infringements through any use of our translation or through your use of any copyrighted material unbeknownst to us.

**Disclaimer of Warranty**

YOU AGREE THAT USE OF COMPANY’S SERVICES AND THE SITE IS AT YOUR SOLE RISK. YOU UNDERSTAND AND AGREE THAT WE DO NOT POSSESS SUFFICIENT EXPERTISE TO PROVIDE SERVICES ITSELF OR EVALUATE THE ACCURACY OR COMPLETENESS OF TRANSLATIONS, FOR THAT WE ENGAGE SERVICE PROVIDERS TO PERFORM THE SERVICES. NEITHER COMPANY, ITS AFFILIATES NOR ANY OF THEIR RESPECTIVE EMPLOYEES, AGENTS, THIRD PARTY CONTENT PROVIDERS OR LICENSORS, OR ANY OF THEIR OFFICERS, DIRECTORS, EMPLOYEES OR AGENTS, WARRANT THAT USE OF THE SITE OR SERVICES WILL BE UNINTERRUPTED OR ERROR FREE. NOR DO THEY MAKE ANY WARRANTIES REGARDING WHETHER OR NOT THE SERVICES MEET YOUR REQUIREMENTS OR AS TO THE ACCURACY, RELIABILITY, OR CONTENT OF ANY INFORMATION OBTAINED FROM THE SITE.

THE SITE AND THE SERVICES ARE PROVIDED ON AN "AS IS" AND AN "AS AVAILABLE" BASIS. COMPANY HEREBY DISCLAIMS ANY AND ALL REPRESENTATIONS, WARRANTIES AND CONDITIONS, WHETHER EXPRESS OR IMPLIED, INCLUDING, BUT NOT LIMITED TO, ANY IMPLIED WARRANTY OF MERCHANTABILITY, FITNESS FOR A PARTICULAR PURPOSE AND NON-INFRINGEMENT.

YOU UNDERSTAND AND AGREE THAT YOUR USE OF ANY MATERIAL AND/OR DATA DOWNLOADED FROM THE SITE OR ANY SERVICES OBTAINED THROUGH OR PROVIDED BY COMPANY IS AT YOUR SOLE DISCRETION AND RISK AND THAT YOU WILL BE SOLELY RESPONSIBLE FOR ANY DAMAGE RESULTING FROM ANY SUCH DOWNLOAD OR USE OF SUCH INFORMATION OR OTHER RELATED TRANSACTION. WE MAKE NO WARRANTY THAT (I) THE SERVICE WILL MEET YOUR REQUIREMENTS, (II) THE SERVICE WILL BE UNINTERRUPTED, TIMELY, SECURE, OR ERROR-FREE, (III) THE RESULTS THAT MAY BE OBTAINED FROM THE USE OF THE SERVICE WILL BE ACCURATE OR RELIABLE, OR (IV) THE QUALITY OF ANY DOCUMENTS, PRODUCTS, SERVICES, INFORMATION, OR OTHER MATERIAL PURCHASED OR OBTAINED BY YOU THROUGH THE SERVICE WILL MEET YOUR EXPECTATIONS.

**Limitation of Liability**

YOU EXPRESSLY UNDERSTAND AND AGREE THAT WE WILL NOT BE LIABLE FOR ANY INDIRECT, INCIDENTAL, SPECIAL, CONSEQUENTIAL, EXEMPLARY DAMAGES, OR DAMAGES FOR LOSS OF PROFITS INCLUDING BUT NOT LIMITED TO, DAMAGES FOR LOSS OF GOODWILL, USE, DATA OR OTHER INTANGIBLE LOSSES (EVEN IF WE HAVE BEEN ADVISED OF THE POSSIBILITY OF SUCH DAMAGES), WHETHER BASED ON CONTRACT, TORT, NEGLIGENCE, STRICT LIABILITY OR OTHERWISE, RESULTING FROM: (I) THE USE OR THE INABILITY TO USE THE SERVICE; (II) THE COST OF PROCUREMENT OF SUBSTITUTE GOODS AND SERVICES RESULTING FROM ANY GOODS, DATA, INFORMATION OR SERVICES PURCHASED OR OBTAINED OR MESSAGES RECEIVED OR TRANSACTIONS ENTERED INTO THROUGH OR FROM THE SERVICE; (III) UNAUTHORIZED ACCESS TO OR ALTERATION OF YOUR TRANSMISSIONS OR DATA; (IV) STATEMENTS OR CONDUCT OF ANY THIRD PARTY ON THE SERVICE; OR (V) ANY OTHER MATTER RELATING TO THE SERVICE. IN NO EVENT WILL COMPANY'S TOTAL LIABILITY TO YOU FOR ALL DAMAGES, LOSSES OR CAUSES OF ACTION EXCEED THE AMOUNT YOU HAVE PAID US IN THE LAST SIX (6) MONTHS, OR, IF GREATER, ONE HUNDRED DOLLARS ($ 100).

SOME JURISDICTIONS DO NOT ALLOW THE EXCLUSION OF CERTAIN WARRANTIES OR THE LIMITATION OR EXCLUSION OF LIABILITY FOR INCIDENTAL OR CONSEQUENTIAL DAMAGES. ACCORDINGLY, SOME OF THE ABOVE LIMITATIONS SET FORTH ABOVE MAY NOT APPLY TO YOU. IF YOU ARE DISSATISFIED WITH ANY PORTION OF THE SERVICE OR WITH THESE TERMS OF SERVICE, YOUR SOLE AND EXCLUSIVE REMEDY IS TO DISCONTINUE USE OF THE SERVICE.

**Indemnification & Release**

You agree to defend, indemnify and hold harmless Company, any parent company, officers, directors, employees and agents, from and against any and all claims and expenses, including but not limited to reasonable attorneys’ fees, arising from your use of the Site and any Translations ordered by User in connection with the Site.

To the extent the law permits, you release us from any and all claims or liability related to the Service, including but not limited to, any action or inaction of a translator/editor, service provider’s failure to comply with applicable law, and failure to accurately perform a service. You agree that you are solely responsible for your interactions with any other user in connection with the Service and we will have no liability or responsibility with respect thereto.

Under no circumstances will we be liable for any loss or damage caused by your reliance on information obtained through Translate.com. It is your responsibility to evaluate the accuracy, completeness of Translations available through our Site and Services.

If you are a California resident, you agree to waive California Civil Code Section 1542, which says: "A general release does not extend to claims which the creditor does not know or suspect to exist in his favor at the time of executing the release, which if known by him must have materially affected his settlement with the debtor." If you are a resident of another jurisdiction, you agree to waive any comparable statute or doctrine.

**Governing Law/Jurisdiction**

All relations shall be governed, construed, and interpreted by, through and under the laws of the State of Delaware, without giving effect to its principles of conflicts of law. In case any claims or disputes arise, they shall be solved in the state and federal courts located in the State of Delaware.

**Termination**

The term of this Agreement begins on the date which you accept and agree to this Agreement. You agree to be bound by this Agreement by submitting an electronic order form for Translations or by subscribing to a monthly or annual plan. You agree that we may suspend, terminate or discontinue the Site at any time without prior notice. We reserve the right to terminate this Agreement at our election and for any reason, without prior notice. We reserve the right to immediately terminate or suspend any User accounts or passwords in the event that User violates any of the terms and conditions of this Agreement or engages in any conduct which we, at our sole discretion, consider to be unacceptable. We may, at our sole discretion and without prior notice, immediately suspend the Service and your account if we determine that you are engaging, or have engaged, in any Abuse of Service to exploit available offerings inappropriately. Abuse of Service includes, but is not limited to, the following actions:

* If you primarily use our Zendesk translation application for translation of incoming requests and fail to do the same for outgoing replies, provided that the number of outgoing replies is lower than 30 (thirty) percent. To ensure that our Zendesk translation application is used effectively, we require both inbound and outbound clients’ messages to be translated via our application. For outbound messages, the minimum threshold that you should not fall below is 30 percent.
* If you create multiple accounts to accumulate benefits from the Freemium features (applies to all types of translation and products). Unauthorized customers and registered users can take advantage of our Service by submitting some small texts for translation free of charge within the specified limits, as a trial run. When you have exhausted the limit and wish to continue using the Service, please consider upgrading to our paid options.
* If you dispute the quality of translation and initiate a chargeback more than 30 (thirty) calendar days after receiving it. Once you have your order, we encourage you to review it and should you need to make a revision request or file a complaint, use the available means of contact. If we don't receive a revision request or complaint regarding the delivered translation within 30 (thirty) calendar days, we implicitly acknowledge that you are satisfied with it and no additional action is required, unless further payment is made, or a new order is submitted.

In the event of any termination, you will immediately cease access to the Site and Services. You agree that Translate.com will not be liable to you or any third-party for any termination of your access to the Service.

**Electronic Communications**

For contractual purposes, you consent to receive communications from us in an electronic form, and agree that all terms and conditions, agreements, notices, disclosures, and other communications that Company provides to you electronically satisfy any legal requirement that such communications would satisfy if it were in writing.

**General**

This Agreement, together with the Privacy Policy at [www.translate.com/legal](https://www.translate.com/legal) and the Pricing Plans, and any other legal notices published by us on the Site, shall constitute the entire agreement between you and Us.

You may not rent, lease, license, grant a security interest in, or otherwise transfer, assign, or sublicense your rights hereunder to any third party.

At any time, we may, in our sole discretion and without providing notice or obtaining your consent, assign this entire Agreement or delegate some or all of its responsibilities hereunder.

**Contact Information**

You may contact us at the following email address: [support@translate.com](mailto:support@translate.com) or through the contact form on the Site.

Privacy Policy for Service Providers
------------------------------------

**Last updated and effective: December 16th, 2024**

**Purpose**

Translate.com LLC ("us", "we", or "our") operates Translate.com website (the "Service").

This page informs you of our policies regarding the collection, use, and disclosure of personal data pertaining to each of our Service Providers in connection with their access and use of our Service and the choices they have associated with that data.

**Information Collection and Use**

We collect several different types of information for various purposes to provide and improve our Service to you in the course of performance of Services of translation, review, or editing of customer content in accordance with Terms & Conditions for Service Providers.

**Types of Data Collected**

**Personal Data**

While using our Service, we may ask you to provide us with certain personally identifiable information that can be used to contact or identify you ("Personal Data").

Personally identifiable information may include, but is not limited to:

* Email address
* First name and last name
* Phone number
* Photo
* Address, State, Province, ZIP/Postal code, City (collected until February, 1, 2022)
* Cookies and Usage Data
* Payment System
* Chosen Payment System Email
* Tax identification information

Your personal data shall be treated in strict confidence. We publish on our Site your first name, photo, languages, and fields of specialization. Other information shall be processed only by Translate.com LLC and its authorized suppliers (i.e., accountants, banks, payment processors etc.), exclusively for the performance of the contract.

**Tracking & Cookies Data**

We use cookies and similar tracking technologies to track the activity on our Service and hold certain information.

Cookies are sent to your browser from a website and stored on your device. Tracking technologies also used are beacons, tags, and scripts to collect and track information and to improve and analyze our Service.

You can adjust the settings within your web browser in accordance with your personal preferences. You can delete cookies that have already been installed at any time and reject new cookies by configuring the settings within your browser. However, if you do not accept cookies, you may not be able to use some portions of our Service.

Examples of Cookies we use:

* Session Cookies. We use Session Cookies to operate our Service.
* Preference Cookies. We use Preference Cookies to remember your preferences and various settings.
* Security Cookies. We use Security Cookies for security purposes.
* Advertising Cookies. Advertising Cookies are used to serve you with advertisements that may be relevant to you and your interests.

**Use of Data**

Translate.com LLC uses the collected data for various purposes:

* To provide and maintain our Service
* To notify you about changes to our Service
* To allow you to participate in interactive features of our Service when you choose to do so
* To provide customer support
* To gather analysis or valuable information so that we can improve our Service
* To monitor the usage of our Service
* To maintain statistics

**Legal Basis for Processing Personal Data Under General Data Protection Regulation (GDPR)**

If you are from the European Economic Area (EEA), Translate.com our legal basis for collecting and using the personal information described in this Privacy Policy depends on the Personal Data we collect and the specific context in which we collect it.

Translate.com LLC may process your Personal Data because:

* We need to perform a contract with you
* You have given us permission to do so
* The processing is in our legitimate interests and it's not overridden by your rights
* For payment processing purposes
* To comply with the law

We will not sell or provide your data to any third party where you have not provided your consent to do so. All other data is processed in accordance with the General Data Protection Regulation (GDPR) 2018 and other applicable laws.

**Retention of Data**

Translate.com LLC will retain your Personal Data only for as long as is necessary for the purposes set out in this Privacy Policy. We will retain and use your Personal Data to the extent necessary to comply with our legal obligations (for example, if we are required to retain your data to comply with applicable laws), resolve disputes, and enforce our legal agreements and policies.

Translate.com LLC will also retain Usage Data for internal analysis purposes. Usage Data is generally retained for a shorter period of time, except when this data is used to strengthen the security or to improve the functionality of our Service, or we are legally obligated to retain this data for longer time periods.

**Transfer of Data**

Your information, including Personal Data, may be transferred to — and maintained on — computers located outside of your state, province, country or other governmental jurisdiction where the data protection laws may differ from those from your jurisdiction.

If you are located outside the United States and choose to provide information to us, please note that we transfer the data, including Personal Data, to the United States and process it there. Your consent to this Privacy Policy followed by your submission of such information represents your agreement to that transfer.

We notify that the country to which personal data is transferred does not provide for an adequate level of data protection based on the European Commission decision. We endeavor to apply suitable safeguards to protect the privacy and security of your personal data and to use it only consistent with your relationship with Us and the practices described in this Privacy Policy.

**Disclosure of Data**

**Business Transaction**

If Translate.com LLC is involved in a merger, acquisition or asset sale, your Personal Data may be transferred. We will provide notice before your Personal Data is transferred and becomes subject to a different Privacy Policy.

**Disclosure for Law Enforcement**

Under certain circumstances, Translate.com LLC may be required to disclose your Personal Data if required to do so by law or in response to valid requests by public authorities (e.g. a court or a government agency).

**Legal Requirements**

Translate.com LLC may disclose your Personal Data in the good faith belief that such action is necessary to:

* To comply with a legal obligation
* To protect and defend the rights or property of Translate.com LLC
* To prevent or investigate possible wrongdoing in connection with the Service
* To protect the personal safety of users of the Service or the public
* To protect against legal liability

**Security of Data**

We implement the most commonly used technical and organizational measures to ensure the protection and security of the data:

* Access control is designed to protect all physical access to the server, client and/or data rooms by using keys, authentication, authorization and other procedures.
* We ensure that all the authorized parties can access only the data specifically related to their specific tasks and/or authorization without being allowed to see anything else.
* If user data is required for analytical and statistical purposes the pseudonymization principle is followed by replacing user-related data by random, anonymous blocks of text.
* We ensure that the data is always transmitted using strong in-transit encryption standards (SSL/TLS certificates). Moreover, other secure connections are used to transfer data from web-based service containing forms, login screens, upload/download capabilities and so on.
* We ensure that all the relevant data is subject to regular backups and also regularly check them to ensure that the data can be successfully retrieved.

The security of your data is important to us, but remember that no method of transmission over the Internet, or method of electronic storage is 100% secure. While we strive to use commercially acceptable means to protect your Personal Data, we cannot guarantee its absolute security.

**"Do Not Track" Signals**

We do not support Do Not Track ("DNT"). Do Not Track is a preference you can set in your web browser to inform websites that you do not want to be tracked. You can enable or disable Do Not Track by visiting the preferences or settings page of your web browser.

**Your Data Protection Rights Under General Data Protection Regulation (GDPR)**

If you are a resident of the European Economic Area (EEA), you have certain data protection rights. Translate.com LLC aims to take reasonable steps to allow you to correct, amend, delete, or limit the use of your Personal Data.

If you wish to be informed what Personal Data we hold about you and if you want it to be removed from our systems, please contact us via email by sending your request to [support@translate.com](mailto:support@translate.com) or through a contact form on the Site.

In certain circumstances, you have the following data protection rights:

* **The right to access,** update or to delete the information we have on you. Whenever made possible, you can access, update or request deletion of your Personal Data directly within your account settings section. If you are unable to perform these actions yourself, please contact us to assist you.
* **The right of rectification**. You have the right to have your information rectified if that information is inaccurate or incomplete.
* **The right to object**. You have the right to object to our processing of your Personal Data.
* **The right of restriction**. You have the right to request that we restrict the processing of your personal information.
* **The right to data portability**. You have the right to be provided with a copy of the information we have on you in a structured, machine-readable and commonly used format.
* **The right to withdraw consent** You also have the right to withdraw your consent at any time where Translate.com LLC relied on your consent to process your personal information.

You have the right to complain to a Data Protection Authority about our collection and use of your Personal Data. For more information, please contact your local data protection authority in the European Economic Area (EEA).

**Service Providers**

We may employ third party companies and individuals to facilitate our Service ("Service Providers"), to provide the Service on our behalf, to perform Service-related services or to assist us in analyzing how our Service is used.

These third parties have access to your Personal Data only to perform these tasks on our behalf and are obligated not to disclose or use it for any other purpose.

* Analytics  
    We may use third-party Service Providers to monitor and analyze the use of our Service.
* Google Analytics  
    Google Analytics is a web analytics service offered by Google that tracks and reports website traffic. Google uses the data collected to track and monitor the use of our Service. This data is shared with other Google services. Google may use the collected data to contextualize and personalize the ads of its own advertising network.You can opt-out of having made your activity on the Service available to Google Analytics by installing the Google Analytics opt-out browser add-on. The add-on prevents the Google Analytics JavaScript (ga.js, analytics.js, and dc.js) from sharing information with Google Analytics about visits activity. For more information on the privacy practices of Google, please visit the Google Privacy & Terms web page: [http://www.google.com/intl/en/policies/privacy/](http://www.google.com/intl/en/policies/privacy/)
* Hotjar  
    Hotjar is a technology service that helps us better understand our users' experience (e.g. how much time they spend on which pages, which links they choose to click, what users do and don't like, etc.) and this enables us to build and maintain our service by means of user feedback. Hotjar uses cookies and other technologies to collect data on our users' behavior and their devices (in particular the IP address of the device (captured and stored only in anonymized form), device screen size, device type (unique device identifiers), browser information, geographic location (country only), preferred language used to display our website). Hotjar stores this information in a pseudonymized user profile. Neither Hotjar nor we will ever use this information to identify individual users or to match it with further data on an individual user. For further details, please see [Hotjar's Privacy Policy](https://www.hotjar.com/legal/policies/privacy).  
    If you do not want to be recorded by Hotjar, you can disable it by setting the DoNotTrack header in your browser. For more information and more about Hotjar's data processing, please visit: [www.hotjar.com/legal/compliance/opt-out](https://www.hotjar.com/legal/compliance/opt-out).
* Advertising  
    We may use third-party Service Providers to show advertisements to you to help support and maintain our Service.
* Google AdSense & DoubleClick Cookie  
    Google, as a third-party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on our Service. Google's use of the DoubleClick cookie enables it and its partners to serve ads to our users based on their visit to our Service or other websites on the Internet.  
    You may opt out of the use of the DoubleClick Cookie for interest-based advertising by visiting the Google Ads Settings web page: [http://www.google.com/ads/preferences/](http://www.google.com/ads/preferences/)
* Ezoic  
    This website uses the services of Ezoic Inc. (“Ezoic”), including to manage third-party interest-based advertising. Ezoic may employ a variety of technologies on this website, including tools to serve content, display advertisements and enable advertising to visitors of this website, which may utilize first and third-party cookies.  
    A cookie is a small text file sent to your device by a web server that enables the website to remember information about your browsing activity. First-party cookies are created by the site you are visiting, while third-party cookies are set by domains other than the one you're visiting. Ezoic and our partners may place third-party cookies, tags, beacons, pixels, and similar technologies to monitor interactions with advertisements and optimize ad targeting. Please note that disabling cookies may limit access to certain content and features on the website, and rejecting cookies does not eliminate advertisements but will result in non-personalized advertising. You can find more information about cookies and how to manage them [here](https://allaboutcookies.org/).  
    The following information may be collected, used, and stored in a cookie when serving personalized ads:
* IP address
* Operating system type and version
* Device type
* Language preferences
* Web browser type
* Email (in a hashed or encrypted form)  
    Ezoic and its partners may use this data in combination with information that has been independently collected to deliver targeted advertisements across various platforms and websites. Ezoic’s partners may also gather additional data, such as unique IDs, advertising IDs, geolocation data, usage data, device information, traffic data, referral sources, and interactions between users and websites or advertisements, to create audience segments for targeted advertising across different devices, browsers, and apps. You can find more information about interest-based advertising and how to manage them [here](https://youradchoices.com/).  
    You can view Ezoic’s privacy policy [here](https://ezoic.com/privacy/), or for additional information about Ezoic’s advertising and other partners, you can view Ezoic’s advertising partners [here](https://www.ezoic.com/privacy-policy/advertising-partners/).

**Payments**

We may provide paid products and/or services within the Service. In that case, we use third-party services for payment processing (e.g. payment processors).

We will not store or collect your payment card details. That information is provided directly to our third-party payment processors whose use of your personal information is governed by their Privacy Policy. These payment processors adhere to the standards set by PCI-DSS as managed by the PCI Security Standards Council, which is a joint effort of brands like Visa, Mastercard, American Express and Discover. PCI-DSS requirements help ensure the secure handling of payment information

We work with Payoneer, Wise, Adv cash, Paxum, Revolut.

We work with PayPal which Privacy Policy can be viewed at [https://www.paypal.com/webapps/mpp/ua/privacy-full](https://www.paypal.com/webapps/mpp/ua/privacy-full)

**Links to Other Sites**

Our Service may contain links to other sites that are not operated by us. If you click on a third-party link, you will be directed to that third party's site. We strongly advise you to review the Privacy Policy of every site you visit.

We have no control over and assume no responsibility for the content, privacy policies or practices of any third-party sites or services.

**Changes to This Privacy Policy**

We may update our Privacy Policy from time to time. We will notify you of any changes by posting the new Privacy Policy on this page.

We will let you know via email and/or a prominent notice on our Service, prior to the change becoming effective and update the "effective date" at the top of this Privacy Policy.

You are advised to review this Privacy Policy periodically for any changes. Changes to this Privacy Policy are effective when they are posted on this page.

**Right to Equal Service**

We will not discriminate against You because you exercised any of your rights, including, but not limited to, by:

* Denying goods or services to you.
* Charging different prices or rates for goods or services, including through the use of discounts or other benefits or imposing penalties.
* Providing a different level or quality of goods or services to you.
* Suggesting that you will receive a different price or rate for goods or services or a different level or quality of goods or services.

**Contact Us**

If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, please contact us:

* By mail: Translate.com LLC, 571 S. Washington, Afton, WY 83110, United States
* By email: [support@translate.com](mailto:support@translate.com) or through a contact form on the Site

Terms & Conditions for Service Providers
----------------------------------------

This Agreement, including these terms and conditions (Terms), constitutes a legally binding agreement between you ("the Service Provider" or "you") and Translate.com LLC. ("Company") (each herein also referred to individually as a "Party," or collectively as the "Parties"), and governs your performance of Services (as defined below). By performing Services, you are consenting to the terms and conditions of this Agreement. If you do not agree to all of the terms of this Agreement, you must not provide Services.

1. **Services & Payment.** In consideration for compensation received, you agree to perform and deliver an accurate and efficient translation from the specified source language into the specified target language, review, or editing of customer content (“Deliverables”) as requested by us from a Translate.com website ("the Site") from time to time (the “Services”). We have the right to check your professional qualification by requesting you to complete an initial test task assigned by Company. We do not restrict your right to choose orders for the translation or editing of a specific content from the Site upon registering your account. You may work on a single order at a time. You shall submit only carefully translated, edited texts without abridgements, additions or other changes in content within the time frame defined by Company.
    
    Payment will be handled in accordance with the published rates we have quoted and provided our customers. Rates are subject to change and are found at the Pricing Page of our Site. Unless otherwise specifically agreed upon by Company in writing (and notwithstanding any other provision of this Agreement), all activity relating to Services will be performed by and only by Service Provider. Service Provider agrees that it will not (and will not permit others to) violate any agreement with or rights of any third party or, except as expressly authorized by Company in writing hereafter, use or disclose at any time Service Provider 's own or any third party's confidential information or intellectual property in connection with the Services or otherwise for or on behalf of Company.
    
    You agree that any compensation you accrue by working under this Agreement will be paid once per month to you via Payoneer, Wise, Adv cash, Paxum, Revolut, PayPal. No other method of payment will be used by us in order to compensate you. Your account must be at a minimum of $ 20 in order for you to cash out via Payoneer, Wise, Adv cash, Paxum, Revolut, PayPal via your account. If you wish to terminate your account and have not yet reached $ 20, please email us at [support@translate.com](mailto:support@translate.com), and we will manually process the Payoneer, Wise, Adv cash, Paxum, Revolut, and PayPal payment for you.
    
2. **Proprietary Information;** Confidentiality. Service Provider shall not use any Confidential or Proprietary Information for any purpose except to evaluate and complete the performance of services related to this Agreement and specific order. Proprietary and Confidential Information includes all Deliverables, and all other business, technical and financial information (including, without limitation, the identity of, personal data and other information relating to customers or employees) developed, learned or obtained by or on behalf of Service Provider during the period that Service Provider is to be providing the Services that relate to Company or Service. Proprietary information also includes information received in confidence by the Company from its customers or suppliers or other third parties. Service Provider shall take reasonable measures to protect the secrecy of and avoid disclosure of any Confidential or Proprietary Information. The duty of confidentiality shall also apply to customers\` personal data contained in the submitted projects.
    
    You may not reproduce or otherwise use or distribute any customer content or information. You agree to treat all customer content in confidence and will be held solely responsible for any damages caused by such a disclosure.
    
    Proprietary Information shall not, however, include any information that Service Provider can establish (i) was publicly known or made generally available without a duty of confidentiality prior to the time of disclosure to Service Provider by us; (ii) becomes publicly known or made generally available without a duty of confidentiality after disclosure to Service Provider by us through no action or inaction of Service Provider; or (iii) is in the rightful possession of Service Provider without confidentiality obligations at the time of disclosure by us to Service Provider as shown by Service Provider ’s records kept in the ordinary course of business. Upon termination or as otherwise requested by Company, Service Provider will promptly provide to Company all items and copies containing or embodying Proprietary Information (including without limitation all Deliverables) or delete them immediately upon request, except that Service Provider may keep its personal copies of its compensation records and this Agreement.
    
3. **Warranties and Other Obligations.** Service Provider represents, warrants and covenants that: (i) the Services will be performed in a professional and workmanlike manner in accordance with current industry standards and practices and that none of such Services nor any part of this Agreement is or will be inconsistent with any obligation Service Provider may have to others; (ii) Service Provider has necessary skills, qualification, and experience to deliver Services; (iii) all work under this Agreement shall be Service Provider 's original work and none of the Services or Inventions nor any development, use, production, distribution or exploitation thereof will infringe, misappropriate or violate any intellectual property or other right of any person or entity (including, without limitation, Service Provider ); (iv) Service Provider may not assign or otherwise transfer this Agreement, by operation of law or otherwise, without the written consent of Company. Any assignment or transfer of this Agreement in violation of the foregoing shall be null and void.
    
4. **Expectations.** You agree to provide quality and reasonably accurate translations under this Agreement in accordance with the standards of quality customary in the translation business, conveying the meaning of the source text by providing either a literal or free translation depending on the source. If you fail to meet our quality standards in your performance under this Agreement, we reserve the right, in our sole discretion, to terminate this Agreement at any time or delete your account. You shall keep your contact and personal account information updated and contact us immediately in the event of a change. We will notify you if we detect fraudulent behavior on your account, explaining the activity that we have detected. Engaging in fraudulent activities, even once, can lead to termination of this Agreement and deletion of your account.
    
5. **Intellectual Property.** You agree that all right, title, and interest in any copyrightable material, including but not limited to all material we receive from you, and arising out of, or in connection with your performance under this Agreement, is the sole property of Translate.com and you reserve no rights in that material.
    
6. **Avoidance of Conflict of Interest.** Service Provider represents and warrants that Service Provider has no outstanding agreement or obligation that is in conflict with any of the provisions of this Agreement, or that would preclude Service Provider from fully complying with the provisions in this Agreement. Service Provider further represents and warrants that Service Provider has full power and authority to enter into this Agreement and perform Service Provider 's obligations hereunder.
    
7. **Term and Termination.** The term of this Agreement begins on the date which you accept and agree to this Agreement. You agree to be bound by this Agreement for every order that you provide your services for. This agreement may be terminated, for any reason, and at any time by you or us. Sections dealing with the handling of Confidential or Proprietary Information and any remedies for breach of this Agreement shall survive any termination or expiration.
    
8. **Relationship of the Parties;** Independent Contractor. For purposes of this agreement and for the services you provide, you will be classified as an independent contractor. You are not an employee, agent, partner or joint venture partner of Company and shall not bind nor attempt to bind Company to any contract. You are not authorized to hold yourself out as an agent of the Company at any time or on any medium. You shall perform services diligently so that any projected time goals set by the customer or the Company are met and reasonably accurate results are obtained for the customer. You shall be solely responsible for determining the method, mode, manner and hours (within the projected timeframe) in which the Services are performed under this Agreement. You are responsible for any expenses incurred by you during the performance of this Agreement. You acknowledge and agree that you are obligated to report all compensation received from us pursuant to this Agreement as income and the obligation to pay any and all taxes on such income is your responsibility. You agree to indemnify the Company from any and all claims, damages, liability, settlement, attorneys' fees and expenses, as incurred, on account of the foregoing or any breach of this Agreement or any other action or inaction by or for or on your behalf.
    
9. **Assignment.** This Agreement and the services contemplated hereunder are personal to Service Provider and Service Provider shall not have the right or ability to assign, transfer or subcontract any rights or obligations under this Agreement without the written consent of Company. Any attempt to do so shall be void. Company may fully assign and transfer this Agreement in whole or part.
    
10. **Electronic Communications.** For contractual purposes, you consent to receive communications from us in an electronic form, and agree that all terms and conditions, agreements, notices, disclosures, and other communications that Company provides to you electronically satisfy any legal requirement that such communications would satisfy if it were in writing.
    
11. **Indemnification.** You agree to indemnify and hold harmless Translate.com and its affiliates and their directors, officers and employees from and against all taxes, losses, damages, liabilities, costs and expenses, including attorneys’ fees and other legal expenses, arising directly or indirectly from or in connection with (i) your negligent, reckless or intentionally wrongful acts, (ii) a determination by a court or agency that you are not an independent contractor, (iii) your breach of any of the covenants contained in this Agreement and other legal terms on the Site, (iv) your failure to perform your duties in accordance with all applicable laws, rules and regulations, or (v) any violation or claimed violation of a third party’s rights resulting in whole or in part from the use of any of your deliverables under this Agreement.
    
12. **Governing Law/Jurisdiction.** All relations shall be governed, construed, and interpreted by, through and under the laws of the State of Delaware, without giving effect to its principles of conflicts of law. In case any claims or disputes arise, they shall be solved in the state and federal courts located in the State of Delaware.
    
13. **Remedy.** Except as provided by the act and this Agreement, arbitration shall be the sole, exclusive, and final remedy for any dispute between Service Provider and the Company. Accordingly, except as provided for by the act and this agreement, neither Service Provider nor the Company will be permitted to pursue court action regarding claims that are subject to arbitration.
    
    Any breach of Section 2 or 3 will cause irreparable harm to Company for which damages would not be an adequate remedy, and therefore, Company will be entitled to injunctive relief with respect thereto in addition to any other remedies.
    
14. **Liability Limitation.** Notwithstanding anything else herein, except for indemnity obligations or breaches of confidentiality, in no event will either party be liable to the other party with respect to this agreement under any legal or equitable theory for (i) any special, indirect, incidental, or consequential damages, or (ii) any amount in the aggregate in excess of the fees paid (or payable) to such party by the other party hereunder.
    
15. **Miscellaneous.** The failure of either party to enforce its rights under this Agreement at any time for any period shall not be construed as a waiver of such rights. In the event that any provision of this Agreement shall be determined to be illegal or unenforceable, that provision will be limited or eliminated to the minimum extent necessary so that this Agreement shall otherwise remain in full force and effect and enforceable. This Agreement, together with the Privacy Policy at [www.translate.com/legal](https://translate.com/legal), and the pricing schedule at [www.translate.com/pricing](http://translate.com/pricing), and any other legal notices published by us on the Site, shall constitute the entire agreement between you and Company.

Business time 7 AM to 4 PM (UTC 0), Mon-Fri.

For Customers

For Business

Resources

Company

Copyright ©2011-2024 TranslateLLC. All rights reserved.

Our cookies

Our website uses cookies to improve your experience. By continuing to use the site you agree to our [Privacy Policy](https://www.translate.com/legal). Approve
